hi this is Alex from fat Li factly needs
a laundry and dry cleaning software for
a laundromat to manage their entire
end-to-end operations whether they have
a single store a multi store or a
franchisee model or aggregator model so
the solution we're going to work across
the bar so as a business you can start
with one store and gradually if you
scale the business to the multi-store
with the plant mode operations the
software will going to support you in in
the whole scaling process a brief intro
about the five clean ease fab clean was
started around the three years back and
we have close to around a 550 customers
managing around close to 1500 plus
stores across India and different parts
of the cloth so coming back to the 2d as
a part of this video we're going to walk
through the store management module as a
laundromat first you come to website and
then sign up through the sign up screen
and you will be given a 14 days free
trial and after that once you go through
all the features and functionality and
then you can convert into the the the
paid version of it so once you sign up
you will be provided with login
credentials after verification of the
OTP so now I am going through with a
sample login module within the Democrat
n chills end-to-end operations so once
you have who user logs in you will be
landed into the the P Y screen from here
you can the store manager can or a store
operator you can create the orders so
before we actually go into the POS let's
observe what is there in the
administration module so administration
has the complete capability
to configure and customize the
application according to your business
needs so initially after you sign up you
end up configuring around three four
entities overall the first one is claims
you might be having a customer data
somewhere in an excel sheet if you are
managing physically or it could be if
you are managing a through one of the
computer application you might going to
have everything in in that application
in that case you can export the data and
import into the party you can either
manually creating the clients or you can
import the data from external party so
coming back to the business account in
business accounts also you can import
the data business accounts is nothing
but if you are if you are providing the
service with the businesses like a
balloon spa hospitals hotels are
transportation companies where the
payment will going to be not in a per
hour basis model it will be once in a
month or once in a or six weeks or seven
weeks so in that case we will be
treating them as a business account and
then the payments will be done through
the batch processor so other thing is
once the sign up you end up configuring
the third one is configuring the whole
Service Catalog
you are providing so fantine support is
a multi-level catalog support so
initially you three layers what you have
a catalogs under the catalog you have a
categories and under the categories you
can define the actual services so you
can have a multiple catalogs define so
if you want it to cater to a different
business model according to your
business model you can create laundry
try cleaning one or car cleaning so some
of our customers not only for the
laundry and dry cleaning business that
is using further they are using for
car cleaning also so the default system
comes up with a default catalog with
their different prices whereas you are
free to change those prices before you
start operating with the farc link you
can do this either by manually editing
them with the surface or you can import
in the whole services from an excel
sheet so you can the color scheme is for
category level so you can edit the
category color or the font color icons
everything the default system comes up
with a bunch of laundry specific icon
but you are free to change according to
your name so coming back to the
priceless priceless see something like
every god you are using for different
customers
so you might really have a customer's
regular customers loyal customers
premium customers it could be something
like in our a section of the based on
the allocation premium location maybe
you can have a read prices so if there
is no limitation in the number of price
list you can define you can define as
many number of price lists as possible
so and also if you have the business
customers you normally signup them with
the contract for a period of time and
then you agree upon particular trade car
in that case so you define the price
list and assign that price Reyes tool
that to the business guy so whenever an
order is created from that business
automatically the price list we're going
to get apply same is the case for even
the clients also so again as to each
point you can also specify them the
prices the price list so when an order
is accepted from that customer
automatically that specific price list
will be created coming back to the
packages packages are nothing but a
prepaid
Glantz which have we are supporting in
the application so we sadly in support
around the five types of different
prepaid plans nothing but packages
weight-based weight-based is more of a
you have package be ticketed given
amount that is around $50 you can
support around 20kg
within a given duration of next one
month with the five visits like that
similarly the the credit based one-click
based is something like you pay around a
thousand bucks and then you get a
services around it
1200 bucks so that means it's an added
extra at 20% additional service will be
provided there is quantity based is
something in the lines of say weight
based one but instead of the kg or LV is
you here you will be mouth monitoring in
terms of the quantity so pay around a
hundred bucks and then you have you are
provided in the service for a quantity
of a maybe 200 clothes like that the
discount based pay around it around at
200 bucks and you will a mile the
service of every order 10% discount so
all 20% discount for a certain duration
type mystery is more of a family type of
package where you have any family
they have around couple and then couple
of kids in that case for trousers five
pant and then two three four studies
like that you can group they create a
package and deliver it to the family all
together so in any of these case the
package are nothing but a prepaid plan
will be useful both for the player as
well as the the business for business
you are getting an interest-free loan in
advance and also the customer is tied up
to you and if you provide the good
service
recurring basis he will keep renewing
this the plan whereas in case of a
customer he be going to be getting the
additional service more than the more
than the yet that the amount paid so it
is mutually beneficial and lot of
customers
the newest trial is getting more and
more moving into the prepaid plans
Fantine comes up with a bunch of
different types of printer support the
garment are printing varmint act
printing is nothing but his bar code
based printing on taffeta roll so
whenever an order is created with a
bunch of garments in it then
automatically it a fatter old printer a
garment tag is printed and then that you
can attach this that the garment tag to
the each and every garment before it
goes to the washer so from that moment
onwards till it get cycle and delivered
to back to the customer this garment rag
will be retained on the with the garment
and it will be used for a tracking needs
so label printing is more of a items
before the packing so for every garment
on the before the packing you attach
this label printing and send it across
to then the customer for a delivery so
you will know in terms of the packing
tracking and also what garment he needs
to within the within the pack you will
know all the details reciprocation
printing is more of a professional the
recept which you will be creaming across
to the either premium customers or to
the the businesses and a consolidated
batch order sold or the one month so in
this case is the loco your address the
the do amount everything is
automatically pops up in the receptor
okay this will be printed on the a4 size
paper are or in terms of the receipt
forms which you normally you're branded
mobile you've ever branded comms but as
thermal printing is more of a printing
which you will be giving across to the
retail retail customers who either who
come to the store or your driver also
can take the Wi-Fi beast or a Bluetooth
based printer along with him to the
customer place for pickups so he can
hand over the the the white garment at
printing sorry thermal printing at the
time of you taking back the clothes from
the customer place so as a as a business
either you can support one two or more
printers by enabling here in the
configuration screen so where as
payments payments we support a couple of
payment gateways stripe for
international payments whereas choice
rupee in the local Indian Indian so a
the payment gateway once it get
configured Fantine plays a role acts of
the payments from the mobile app as well
as that the online receipt which were
going to be sent across to the customer
through the Watsa so any amount which we
are going to be receive it will be
directly deposited into your accounts so
triggers triggers are nothing but a
notification events which will be
configured by default the system comes
up with a a dozen or more than dozen
notification types as a business you
want you to add of additional things you
can create keep creating it so far clean
supports around four types of
notifications one is email
the other one is SMS web push mobile
push as well as Watsa so there is no
limitation in the number of notification
or messages you can sent a class for any
given particular event and there are a
bunch of tokens available in terms of
the order data as well as the customer
data you click on that you get this data
into the content and whenever the knee
happens the whole message will going to
be get farm dream by replacing those
tokens with the actual data and sent to
the customer so you can configure the
different taxes according to your
country and then um accordingly
the taxes will going to get applied on
the services so plant mode operations so
right now I will going to walk through
the plant mode operations at later stage
but if you wanted to attach a plant to a
given stroll here is where you create a
plan and then attach to this plan did
this tour so from here onwards the plant
to store so to plant communication will
going to happen with the Delaware each
alarms tracking government tracking
everything in terms of in the operations
are concerned so for a single store
module which if you don't have any plant
mode operations you don't need to worry
on this ok coming back to the loyalty
points and referral program and
discounts you know in the membership
points live the points is nothing but a
membership points which can be given to
the customers based on the loyalty and
recurring orders they are placing with
the business ok so if you have multiple
orders in a Kinnaman month and the
customer is keep recurring giving the
recurring orders in that case a loyalty
points for you going to keep bubbling up
according to the definition here that
you can allow the customers to redeem
them ok whereas a different program is
something like it if one customer wanted
to he is referring the other customers
because as a business you want to give a
benefit in terms of the points to both a
referral as well as the referral so in
terms of in case of the referral maybe
you wanted to give in the next order or
in case of the referral you can give it
in their first hunter also ok tax is
going to work according to the the
definition here whereas the promo code
or a discount is whenever you
miss a dip in the business you wanted to
announce a new discount coupons and then
publish them were the campaign's so
automatically when the campaign actually
received some of the customers might
want to feel interest based on the
coupon and then if they just ordering
the coupon through the coupon then as a
business owner you know which coupons
are circling better and then based on
that analytics you need the point of
time you can plan the next set of
coupons arrive at your business but each
coupon is we have around the support for
a percentage based as well as that
simple amount based so and also there is
an expiration start and end dates so
that the coupon will going to work in
those durations only so coming back to
the staff the whole application we are
going to comes up with a default set of
roles and permissions but as a as a
business you wanted to have your own new
roles and then set up permissions
according to that you still can define
all the functionality of the application
is divided into a bunch of features and
you are given an access to
enable/disable the features for a given
role the system comes up with the owner
that means to have driver but if we
wanted to have a work area manager or if
you wanted to create it and a cash flow
manager or an accountant you still can
create much another row and of the row
and then assign the bunch of other
permissions to it then automatically
when that person belongs to that role
vlogs in only those specific features
and functionality is enabled so there is
an attendance concept also with this a
tendency is more abstract through the
mobile app Fantine also comes up with a
mobile app for so people as well as the
drivers as well as the your customers so
your start we're going to be using one
of the store module
so rap or a driver in any either of the
case there is a there is a feature
called like unions so you can as a staff
guy you can check in check out the time
of check-in check the five teen a mobile
app track the location of the the person
where he is checking in checking out and
also calculate cumulative time at
indicating how much time he is within
the sole in terms of a total duration is
concerned so if the people are checking
in from outside then it you're going to
let you know which address so you can
easily figure out the people are from
checking outside and then you can
control the login operations also so
coming back to the administration and
the configuration so system comes up
with you can set your time zone your
currency your date format and language
athlean support around half a dozen
languages so that all your total mobile
apps will be going to be in in your
respective language the brining
configuration you can upload your local
ferret on and then business team and
also business servers so beach day of
the business you are off and working
days holidays so based on this your fab
team mobile app we're going to function
so whenever a customer tried to book an
order it will only allow within the
business days and also if it is already
it won't allow them to book an order
because you're drivers won't be allowed
it won't be there because you are not
working on that it the address details
you which are the address details you
are entered here they will be visible
both in your website as well as in terms
of in mobile app the system comes up
within online store one online store
where where you can take if you retire
your to mine to one of this store which
will have is going to act as a default
store and you can capture the order
your mobile app itself or from your
website itself so if you already have a
dumb mine then you and don't have a
website you can use the default website
if you don't have a domain also but you
can use this URL to capture orders from
the customer directly okay so it has it
supports both a complete a place an
order with all the garments as a
customer or you once the administration
and configuration is over then if you
are you and your team is ready to use
the solution both POS and other
functionality so as a store
administrator or a storefront as guy is
mostly using the P voice to capture them
orders from the customers who are
stepping into the store or for the
customers who are making a online or a
phone call and asking you to create a
big producer so now because all the
orders all the all the client data is
inputted into the system already so if
the customer is already into the system
then you can search the customer using
their phone number or through the name
and address in any of the scenario so
the matching customers will be going to
be displayed over here and you pick up
one of the customer if the customer is
not in the store then you use this new
customer link to actually create a new
customer and then and then order on
behalf of him so whereas if the customer
is already existing in the store you can
use the the customer matching with that
number then from that you are ready to
capture order based on the garments we
actually take into the brought it to the
store so the delivery date here is
automatically pop
based on the configuration which you did
it at the administration section if you
notice there are three icons here the
icon red indicates the past history of
the customer the customer already made
around of four five orders with us and
two of them harder to achieve until over
and he has unpaid amount in that case it
is showing red so when the customer
comes to the store if he is showing red
means you can ask there is a chilly
amount for the customer you can ask him
if you wanted to edit the any customer
data at any point of time you can use
the edit icon and based on the customer
name if you want it - such as the
existing packages then packages are
nothing but prepaid plans you can
suggest him so that the customer will go
in to buy that will be always safe added
extra revenue for you Pete our advanced
revenue for you okay so and also based
on the type of the customer you wanted
to choose one of these price list then
automatically the price specified in
that price list will go into Kaplan the
good point is on the left side all the
icons with the rates and the fabric name
is displayed as the customer your staff
need not be a indicated in our to read
Alden a language because the icons
itself is indicating enough to figure
out which government is the Left panel
is completely a touch-based module so if
you keep like touching it in the number
of garments will be keep incrementing
and also you can either change the
quantity or you can keep clicking on it
any of these scenario
it's it's a quick enter for the the
front desk I at the time of garment you
also wanted to capture few other
information again as to the garment in
that case there is a vertical three
dotted icon which indicates what is the
color of the fabric or is there any
strains in there or is there any extra
work needs to be done by living on
stitching
teaching and extra amount around 30 20
bucks you can you can capture that so
automatically it will going to be
populated over here and the same thing
we're going to come in the belly same
thing if you're going to come in the
garment tax also so that guys who are
working at the work area know exactly
what to do with the given garner okay so
and then if all the fabric are captured
then you are ready to check out so if
you check out then it'll go into that
showcase you if he has any credits in
advance into his account if you show
that if not if he wanted to pay in
advance amount then you can keep capture
the partial at once amount also for
example you were 200 rupees then rest of
the amounts is going to be displayed
over here you can you can beat the
pavement without payment Union a with
pay is indicating that or the full
amount will be taken without pay with
pay both the options will going to give
and taken at the other time so once the
order is created it showcase that means
that you can print the garments manually
or you can print the garment tags
manually or automatically as defined in
the configuration if you notice if you
click on the wats app icon what's up I
can be going to showcase that send the
order to the customer this phone number
through your business whatsapp account
so this is how the the overall data will
be sent it across if the customer takes
on this Lane which is either through his
mobile number
mobile phone or it could be laptop then
the overall complete will be going to
get displayed for him like this so if it
is a mobile then the whole bill will be
displayed in a mobile responsive way as
I as in your customer he can pay you the
money through the bailiff there are a
bunch of netbanking bunch of credit card
and just a ballot our supported UPN
supported so you as a whatever the
options you want you to contribute you
can configure it but any amount which
will be
chill will be automatically sent it'll
pass through your Bangkok
so once the payment and the delivery is
being made this paling is actually be
faced with it with you so that you can
capture the review from your customers
online so now coming back to that once
the order is created you can use this
icon to actually recreate the one more
order for a different customer who isn't
the truth okay so in any of the scenario
suppose if you want it to customer is on
the phone then you want to capture
customer pick up order in that case you
don't need to capture any garment just
take the driver and the pickup time
automatically it will be quick there's a
pickup model and we're going to come and
displayed over here in the pickup
section if the earlier order will come
under the in process such if you notice
he comes and in process as a short
thicker links on the top other
indicating what are the pickups needs to
be done today what are the cups needs to
be then feature feature and then the
mail feature like a tomorrow day after
tomorrow
what are the pickups which is supposed
to be done but not time is module okay
so if any and the pickup is will
showcase in your head then every date
has a fact then that indicates that they
never read it also promise but you can
pick up that so similarly if now you can
export all these orders and also
whenever you assign the pickup to a
driver then automatically driver will
going to get the notification in his
mouth while because driver will be using
game of viola something like mobile apps
are there in the app store so that you
can ask you a favor to download this app
whenever there is a map I pick up is
actually assigned to him we will know so
he is mobile you know all the paper
actually supposed to be doing all the
calories
supposed to be doing today me models we
need implants to be long so based on
this driver you're going to go to the
customer please take that other giggle
aids and make sure pickup is open that
particular specifically picked up and
put on the garment and send the bill to
the walks at itself so we here as at
Raylan you can send that drastically too
much one to the water the other way is
the fact T Mobile our support
travel app supports bluetooth in its
culture so there are around printers
with a range of 30 to 50 dollars you can
give one group of this printer to the
customer so enjoyable so that when he
goes to the customer previously the
customer insists on giving the physical
bill you can use that good filter to
actually print the code similarly the
customer also Calculon actually use the
mobile app the party can jumera the
consumer so if he wanted to use your
store number and feel anything to the
store and then you can create a pickup
or our place and all the math on behalf
of himself it's like so in either of
these scenario so a pickup request will
be created and placed into the store in
the pickup system so you pick ups there
are three well Gardens are there one
automatically assigning the teacups with
an existing various in the wrong dragon
or automatically assigned to the ticket
to the near area the guy who is running
around if the guy is allocated to a
certain area code then automatically if
the pickup is coming from that area for
it will be automatically assigned even
that specific fiber but 15 mobile app
that teen consumer party business app or
the driver are both of them comes with
it as a part of the subscription plan
itself as free so coming back to the
intro search for a picker if you notice
if the customer is in any process more
also the orders are in cross smooth
you can see whatever the guy who is
assigned to the in process with an
everything Artemis of the package replay
another then you have this fact and also
there are a bunch of options are nested
order so this indicates you can capture
the partial payment techniques to the
order or you can do a partial delivery
to the order or you can send a whatsapp
message or SM especially right then and
there itself but you can do if you want
it to print it front door research you
still can do it so if the cleaning is
done in the work area is the guy who is
assigned to it will going to be mark
this order has it clean
he still can do it both is mobile app as
well as to the laptop or desktop to a
standard what carrier section if he the
user clicks on the clean then it
automatically comes into the ready state
so he is about karyotype we can do the
marking the order says it complete team
into much one by clicking on the clean
bike on our through the garments
spanning section through the barcode
scanner
if we keep scanning then automatically
the orders we're going to keep moving
into the right side and if you say clean
then if all the garments within the cave
and order are gained then the MA are we
going to marked as clean and move into
the we move into the very strict so with
this the order flow you can manage track
the garments
performance of the you judge we're
screening and performance of the toilets
we is picking up all that will be
captured effortlessly whereas the other
one is a geo tracking geo tracking is
nothing but if you place any order into
the system into the pickup then your
drivers are going to do some mobile apps
go to the customer a scientific paper
fine so for that the geo tracking is
enabled in the driver mobile app so just
like a mini point you can track where
the driver side in the same lines as
business wanna you can track your
drivers be it they are so if the pick up
pace that the symbol of this very handy
is perfect up similarly for a delivery
there is a different icon so the red can
indicate the pink appeals is what would
you if the pickup is within the time
then it will show the green bathing
makeup leaving hand icon so just like an
open you can track here give a flavor
shot and make it information just like
over you have a complete control on the
flavor so now with the bitter with the
geo tracking enabled and but I was
carrying a mobile app you don't need to
call the drivers to find out where they
are so basically from this map itself
you can completely overview you want LOH
you will pick up your driver such as in
each not and make it information assign
the proper pickups to the proper drivers
who are in that way ok this is very
useful if you wanted to do it on demand
gallery an on demand water whereas the
campaign is nothing but the CRM built
into the system so if you wanted to send
it class Pushpam times if you wanted to
send the class to the customers SMS
campaign you can read the numbers but
you can send it across to the existing
client and then make measure which
campaign is doing properly so the other
section is expenses section
expenses will going to give you the
overall picture in terms of that the
spending happening in the store level if
you have if you don't have a control on
the extensors normally you're spending
vocals up over the period of time and
you don't have any any control on the
the business so the proper way of doing
the things is this the same expenses is
also enabled the functionality is
enabled to the mobile app to the mobile
app so as a mob from the mobile app you
can also capture your your team can also
capture that in
sorry expenses so beat the expenses
being captured normally you can do it
inside stronger line like which category
we are spending more money which staff
user is spending more money and which
vendor here we are paying more all the
details moving it out at one shot
normally if there is a leak hey this
happens in the stores at three different
places number one one customers Gardner
goes to the other customer in that case
it's a you are expending our money
in terms of a reimbursement so that can
be avoided using the garnet that printed
what we discussed whereas here the other
section evening AG's expenses until
unless you have a control or a complete
expenses are fitted into the system
normally link is a patch that because of
various various ways one because of the
negligence of the staff or some people
might going to want to add a real
intention of stealing the money in any
of these scenarios your business is
getting affected the third very
practical module that comes up with a
party nails is inventory normally
inventory you have a lot of precious
materials in under the business package
shared car materials anchors package you
make even scan accounts all of them you
might be buying from various vendors so
at any point of time if you are having a
multiple stores and you are as a
business owner out of the store and you
wanted to find out what is your event
will about me that can be completely
packed and controlled if you have a
little thing feeding into the system so
you can generate the purchase orders
send a class to the customer your
vendors and once the material is leasing
your inventory goes bubbles up and which
vendors you are sending the purchase
orders which of them are at what stage
how many of them are receiving stage how
many of them are pending stage payment
stage
you all can know okay if you are
managing multiple stores so if what one
point one store you have an inventory
and the other soul you don't have
instead of buying the inventory or the
other store through actually order you
can transfer the inventory from one
store together so automatically
inventory levels across both the stores
were you going to pull up a big limit
according T based on the that the
transfers happen similarly the other
leakage thirdly kgs until unless you
have a control or hard it happens every
once in a two weeks or once in a week
then it is always difficult for other
people to there is always a linkage
happening in terms of the inventory is
concerned the materials are precious
because of the negligence are stealing
stealing intentions some sort of a this
materials will going to be you start
losing it
the moment you have audit happening and
capturing all the any small miss
adjustments in the inventory level so
over the period of time you have a
hardened happening your staff also
consciously know that if something is
done or not handled properly which we
going to get cop cart or UN they end up
giving an explanation and they were
going to pay attention so that your
inventory will going to be always always
properly utilized and he will be you
won't be losing any money or the period
okay the final and critical section is
the insights though there is a lot of
business in the overall like capturing
orders processing orders delivering
orders notifications expense capturing
and then deliveries in terms of the geo
tracking inventory purchase orders
vendor management everything is there
but still if you have don't have
insights proper insights you don't know
how what the health after your business
is so the order some of you pick up
somebody tell every is would you all
these widgets we're going to change
based on the curation which you select
on the top okay
the the summary it will give you the
summary in terms of what's the business
is doing in terms of the auto stock
answer the five critical elements like a
orders packages and your four months
your customers and then if at all there
is a payments come
you will review mechanism performance
the insights we're going to give you
through these five different angles
through the complete business so if you
wanted to see compare of your fearing it
in different durations this month with
the last month in that case we can
select side by side check the orders
find out there are various reports in
terms of the revenue orders top
customers top-selling items you can
select that particular duration for this
month the last month of this month the
next month and then you can make around
a comparison and making formal tations
if you click on this any of this you're
going to go to that specific list of
payments or customers or orders you can
export them through the searching alls
so whereas this one inventory and
Finance from ANSI is more of a how much
is that revenue you are making how much
is the tax amount how much are the
expenses if the drivers are also
collecting the physical money to the
customers how much is the drivers
collected money which is not handed out
to the store level another thing you
will know how to overview and then you
click on that you will going to get into
the details so if you are capturing the
payments through various payment modes
even know which payment mode you are
capturing how much money so there is a
duration amount across this duration
which it will going to be give you you
want to capture this whole data and
analyze it for a given you region you
select this box and then check it out
accounts is nothing but it your insights
about the customer how many customers
painting or during one time two times
three times a given duration or if the
customer is not ordering anything in any
given duration he is in the verge of
losing so you know exactly you want to
create a promotional order and then send
it across to the customer and try to
capture it again regain the customer you
still can do it through the campaign for
all the inactive customer inactive
customer star first my soda doesn't give
the business business within this month
or two months according to the duration
which you selected here there is a
miscellaneous reports in terms of it how
is the staff performance always the
drivers perform
mr. what carrier people performance how
many garments they actually processes
within the given duration which of the
which of the items you are getting more
money which of the services you are
getting more money which of the
customers is generating them more
revenue for you in terms of a ravine who
is giving the positive feedback who is
giving the negative feedback what is the
problem with the feedback and according
to the feedback you can include your
selfies so if any total retail customers
how many of them are rightly points
painting a class so that this is nothing
but your it services your liable because
you promised to the people based on the
loyalty point you if you don't serve
them right so you can set across the
exploration modes for them and
accordingly make a business out
similarly packages packages they are
nothing but the prepaid plans that is
one of the critical business model which
is a much in these days
so we at any point of time how much
revenue you brought through the packages
which are the packages at the verge of
expiration and what all the customers
were expired so that the system we are
going to automatically send across the
notifications to the customers using the
packages in the virtue of pass one week
of the package for exploration so then
it will try to push them to actually be
subscribed to the the same package or a
different package so the campaign or a
notification if you're going to sue you
to retain the customer so at any point
of time if you customer comes to your
store and wanted to search use the order
number of phone number you can search
the orders there is an advanced search
option here to actually indicating you
search the customer various filters you
can search the orders various filters
you can search the payments based on the
mode or the different filters at any
point of time all the search data you
can export and analyze and then make
addictions
so if you notice once you have a sign up
for a company or a store to have an
end-to-end administration you can define
your catalog important define import
your customer
create your staff and start creating the
others happiness to them track your
drivers to the mobile apps and then send
the notification to the customers to
learn different modes of notifications
like you mean SNS and whatsapp and
analyze the whole data using the
insights and anything happening in there
in terms of inventories cancer know them
even from the mobile apps as well as
tracking to the papaya so for a store to
manage end to end our patient this
platform has everything so to summarize
we have the business we are in the
business for the last three years and we
have close to around 1500 flash stores
under the management across the
different phases from the globe okay so
if you have any questions please don't
hesitate to reach out to our support and
we review the numbers in the future
bottom to the email or through the water
so if you have any of the questions in
terms of the data or content is
concerned you can visit the path teen
app you can find out the overall all the
features and functionality finally if
you have your own website you still can
capture the data by jesus washbowl is
one of the customer we can this book now
which if this is coming this is video t
is nothing but of factly enrichment so
you can get down effortlessly with the
piece of code you can capture the orders
from the left evil website also we also
provide the white labeled apps for your
business if you want to give it your
home Whitely will have like me to wash
the laundry here what experts there are
of companies
taken a by table apps from us so
so that you don't need to expose the
octane brand to your customers
so please please reach out to us with
any questions thanks for watching the
video